

CAROLINE PIMENTA

videomaker

Telephone

+351 967209039

Email

caroline@carolinepimenta.eu www.carolinepimenta.eu

Website Skype

pimentacaroline

About Me

I am a professional videomaker based in Lisbon, Portugal.
I graduated in Communication Science and have been working in video production since 2008.
I specialized in short documentaries, my main clients being third sector organisations with a clear social concern. Most of my films so far have focused on human development projects and life stories.

Skills

Editing

Experience

FREELANCER VIDEOMAKER

2010-Present

I usually deliver a full package of video services - scriptwriting, interviews, footage, animations and subtitles. I shoot, edit and manage the online publishing of the contents I produce.

JOURNALIST

2008-2010

Produced TV reports about immigration and multiculturalism for "Nós" programme at RTP2.

Education

COMMUNICATION SCIENCE

2005-2008

Instituto Superior de Ciências Sociais e Políticas Universidade de Lisboa

VIDEO PRODUCTION

2010-Present

Technical training: Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe After Effects, Kdenlive Video Editor, Audacity Sound Editor, GIMP Image Manipulation Program, Subtitle Editor.

Interests

Entrepreneurship and social innovation, intergenerational projects, migrations, education and human rights. I'm available for work commissions abroad or I can work remotely from Lisbon.

Clients

Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation

Ashoka Portugal

Agah Kahn Foundation

Instituto Padre António Vieira

PORTFOLIO